Washingtoniana Periodicals Collection Periodicals
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Washingtoniana Periodicals Collection
1866-2017
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Periodicals
250 Linear feet
- 1812 Bulletin of the Society of the War, 1935-11 - 1942-10 (Box A001)
- African Shopper, 1999-05 - 2003-12 (Box A002)
- African Shopper, 2004-02 - 2007-01 (Box A003)
- American Assoc of University Women, 1950-01 - 1955-12 (Box A004)
- American Assoc of University Women, 1962-09 - 1970-12 (Box A005)
- American Eagle News, 1999-01-18 - 2005-10-19 (Box A006)
- Americanization Bulletin, 1922-02 - 1948-12 (Box A007)
- Americanization Bulletin, 1923-12-01 - 1930-11 (Box A008)
- Architecture DC, 2004 - 2008 (Box A009)
- Architecture DC, 2012 - 2014 (Box A010)
- Architecture DC, 2015 - 2016 (Box A011)
- Arkansas Traveler, 1940-03-15 - 1963-02 (Box A012)
- Arts Club Washington, 1946-12 - 1965-12 (Box A013)
- Arts Washington, 1982-11 - 2000-01 (Box A014)
- Asian Fortune, 1994-08 - 2003-12 (Box A015)
- Asian Fortune, 2004-01 - 2008-04 (Box A016)
- Atlantic and Pacific News-Times, The, 1942-11-18 - 1946-02 (Box A017)
- Atlantic Naturalist, 1950-09 - 1975 (Box A018)
- Atlantic Naturalist, 1950-11 - 1965-12 (Box A019)
- Atlantic Naturalist, 1966-01 - 1970 (Box A020)
- Atlantic Naturalist, 1971 - 1976 (Box A021)
- Audubon Naturalist, 2007-07 (Box A022)
- A - Misc 1 (Box A023)
- A - Misc 2 (Box A024)
- Bar Report, 1980-03 - 1991-09 (Box B001)
- Bar Report, 1991-12 - 1996-05 (Box B002)
- Bar Report, 1997-02 - 1999-09 (Box B003)
- Barstool, 1998-10-13 - 2000-03-07 (Box B004)
- Beacon, The, 2006-07 - 2007-12 (Box B005)
- Beacon, The, 2008-01 - 2008-12 (Box B006)
- Beacon, The, 2009-01 - 2009-12 (Box B007)
- Beacon, The, 2010-12 - 2015-09 (Box B008)
- Blue Prints National Building Museum, 1981 - 1999 (Box B009)
- Board of Trade Newsletter, 1965-07 - 1972-03 (Box B010)
- Broadcast Pioneers Library, 1986 - 1990 (Box B011)
- Brookland-Woodbridge Guide, 1932-05 - 1934-12 (Box B012)
- Brookland-Woodbridge Guide, 1935-01 - 1938-12 (Box B013)
- Brookland-Woodbridge Guide, 1942-01 - 1944-10 (Box B014)
- Brookland-Woodbridge Guide, 1945-10-18 - 1949-05-12 (Box B015)
- Brookland-Woodbridge Guide, 1945-10-11 - 1946-12-26 (Box B016)
- Buenas Noticias, 1986-02 - 1993-06 (Box B017)
- Buglar, The, 1985-12 - 1996-02-23 (Box B018)
- Building Washington, 1987 - 1994-12 (Box B019)
- Building Washington, 1995-03 - 2005 (Box B020)
- Building Washington, 2006 - 2008 (Box B021)
- Building Washington, 2009 - 2016 (Box B022)
- Bulletin (Junior Chamber of Comm.), 1950-06 - 1953-01 (Box B023)
- Bulletin (Medical Society of DC), 1931-01 - 1931-12 (Box B024)
- Bulletin of the National...Garden Clubs, 1967-09 - 1976-04 (Box B024)
- Bulletin Board, 1993-02 - 1996-04 (Box B025)
- Bulletin of the High School Teachers, 1909-12 - 1943 (Box B026)
- Bulletin of the High School Teachers, 1949-05 - 1955-05 (Box B027)
- Bulletin of the Philosophical Society, 1888 - 1894 (Box B028)
- Bulletin of the Philosophical Society, 1895 - 1899 (Box B029)
- Bulletin, The (DC Bankers Association), 1929-08 - 1932-04 (Box B030)
- Bulletin, The (Wash. Board of Trade), 1920 - 1946-08 (Box B031)
- Burroughs Bulletin (Woodridge), 1935-10 - 1936-10 (Box B032)
- Business Review, 1982-02-22 - 1983-07-29 (Box B033)
- Business Review, 1983-08-01 - 1983-12-23 (Box B034)
- Business Review, 1984-01-02 - 1984-04-27 (Box B035)
- Business Review, 1984-04-03 - 1984-08-03 (Box B036)
- Business Review, 1984-08-06 - 1984-11-02 (Box B037)
- Business Review, 1984-11-05 - 1985-03-29 (Box B038)
- Business Review, 1985-03-25 - 1985-07-19 (Box B039)
- Business Review, 1985-07-22 - 1986-01-03 (Box B040)
- Business Review, 1985-12-30 - 1986-07-04 (Box B041)
- Business Review, 1986-07-07 - 1987-01-02 (Box B042)
- Business Review, 1987-01-05 - 1987-06-05 (Box B043)
- B - Misc 1 (Box B044)
- B - Misc 2 (Box B045)
- C and P Call, The, 1930-01 - 1969-12 (Box C001)
- Calendar of the Week (Council of DC), 1988-01-07 - 1989-12-24 (Box C002)
- Capital Baptist, 1968-01-04 - 1970-01-16 (Box C003)
- Capital Baptist, 1970-01-01 - 1971-12-16 (Box C004)
- Capital Baptist, 1972-01-13 - 1975-08-21 (Box C005)
- Capital Baptist, 1976-04-08 - 1984-12-20 (Box C006)
- Capital Baptist, 1985-01-24 - 1993-11-18 (Box C007)
- Capital Baptist, 1994-01 - 2007-10 (Box C008)
- Capital Baptist, 2008-09 - 2009-01 (Box C009)
- Capital "A Weekly Review", The, 1903-11-07 - 1903-12-19 (Box C010)
- Capital Chemist, The, 1951-01 - 1978-04 (Box C011)
- Capital Counciler, The, 1966-09 - 1973-06 (Box C012)
- Capital Sports Focus, 1989-02 - 1990-12 (Box C013)
- Capital Spotlight, 1975-01-02 - 1976-12-16 (Box C014)
- Capital Spotlight, 1977-03-03 - 1977-09-15 (Box C015)
- Capital Spotlight, 1978-01-12 - 1978-12-28 (Box C016)
- Capital Spotlight, 1979-01-04 - 1979-12-27 (Box C017)
- Capital Spotlight, 1980-01-03 - 1980-12-25 (Box C018)
- Capital Spotlight, 1981-01-08 - 1981-12-24 (Box C019)
- Capital Spotlight, 1982-01-14 - 1982-12-30 (Box C020)
- Capital Spotlight, 1983-01-06 - 1983-12-29 (Box C021)
- Capital Spotlight, 1984-01-05 - 1984-12-20 (Box C022)
- Capital Spotlight, 1985-01-03 - 1985-11-28 (Box C023)
- Capital Spotlight, 1986-01-02 - 1986-12-25 (Box C024)
- Capital Spotlight, 1987-01-01 - 1987-06-04 (Box C025)
- Capital Spotlight, 1987-06-11 - 1987-12-24 (Box C026)
- Capital Spotlight, 1988-01-07 - 1988-07-14 (Box C027)
- Capital Spotlight, 1988-07-21 - 1988-12-29 (Box C028)
- Capital Spotlight, 1989-01-05 - 1989-12-28 (Box C029)
- Capital Spotlight, 1990-01-18 - 1990-12-27 (Box C030)
- Capital Spotlight, 1991-01-03 - 1991-06-27 (Box C031)
- Capital Spotlight, 1991-07-04 - 1991-12-19 (Box C032)
- Capital Spotlight, 1992-01-02 - 1992-12-31 (Box C033)
- Capital Spotlight, 1993-01-07 - 1993-06-24 (Box C034)
- Capital Spotlight, 1993-07-01 - 1994-12-28 (Box C035)
- Capital Spotlight, 1995-01-19 - 1996-12-19 (Box C036)
- Capital Spotlight, 1996-04-18 - 1999-12-2 (Box C037)
- Capital Spotlight, 2000-01-20 - 2002-08-22 (Box C038)
- Capital Style, 1997-10 - 2000-05 (Box C039)
- Capitol File, 2005 - 2007 (Box C040)
- Capitol Hill News, 1961-12 - 1968-01 (Box C041)
- Capitol Hill Spectator, The, 1962-09-18 - 1971-08-26 (Box C042)
- Cathedral Age, 1925 - 1945 (Box C043)
- Cathedral Age, 1946 - 1968 (Box C044)
- Cathedral Age, 1969 - 1975 (Box C045)
- Cathedral Age, 1969 - 1980 (Box C046)
- Cathedral Age, 1981 - 1989 (Box C047)
- Cathedral Age, 1990 - 1996 (Box C048)
- Cathedral Age, 1997 - 2004 (Box C049)
- Cathedral Age, 2005 - 2016 (Box C050)
- Cathedral Chimes, 1907 - 2003 (Box C051)
- Catholic Standard, 1995-06-27 - 1999-12-30 (Box C052)
- Catholic Standard, 2000-01-06 - 2001-12-27 (Box C053)
- Catholic Standard, 2002-01-03 - 2004-12-30 (Box C054)
- Catholic Standard, 2005-01-06 - 2008-07-17 (Box C055)
- Center Line (Washington Hospital Ctr), 1959-06 - 1970-11 (Box C056)
- Center Line (Washington Hospital Ctr), 1972-06 - 1980-10 (Box C057)
- Certificate, The, 1941-12 - 1982-12 (Box C058)
- Childrens Hospital Arrow, The, 1903-06 - 1952-09 (Box C059)
- Chronicle, The (Hampshire Heights), 1939-02 - 1942-11 (Box C060)
- Church Militant, The, 1922-04 - 1924-03 (Box C061)
- Citizen, The (Columbia Heights), 1925-06-02 - 1933-01-03 (Box C062)
- City Club Tribune, 1920-01-20 - 1924-12-20 (Box C063)
- City Club Tribune, 1925 - 1928-09 (Box C064)
- City Club Tribune, 1928-10-06 - 1930-05-30 (Box C065)
- City News (D.C. Government), 1978-03 - 1978-12 (Box C066)
- Cityscape, 1974-10 - 1981-10 (Box C067)
- Cleveland Park Voices, 1991 - 2001 (Box C068)
- Clinical Proceedings Children's Hosp., 1949-12 - 1953-12 (Box C069)
- Clinical Proceedings Children's Hosp., 1954 - 1975 (Box C070)
- Clinical Proceedings Children's Hosp., 1976 - 1978 (Box C071)
- Collectors Club of Washington, The, 1937 - 1956 (Box C072)
- Colonial Times, 1971 - 1972 (Box C073)
- Columbia Heights News, 1930 - 1933 (Box C074)
- Columbian, 1972 - 1977 (Box C075)
- Columbian Call, 1897 - 1898 (Box C076)
- Come Hostelling, 1971 - 1979 (Box C077)
- Common Denominator, The, 1986 - 1999 (Box C078)
- Common Denominator, The, 2000 - 2006 (Box C079)
- Community News (Howard University), 1983 - 1992 (Box C080)
- Community News (Howard University), 1993 - 1997 (Box C081)
- Community News (Howard University), 1998 - 2001 (Box C082)
- Community UPO, 1975 - 1981 (Box C083)
- Compass, The (Columbia Tech Inst), 1936 - 1950 (Box C083)
- Corby Magazine, 1915 - 1919 (Box C084)
- Corcoran Gallery of Art Bulletin, The, 1947 - 1968 (Box C085)
- Corridor Real Estate Journal, The, 1992 - 1992 (Box C086)
- Corridor Real Estate Journal, The, 1993 - 1993 (Box C087)
- Corridor Real Estate Journal, The, 1994 - 1995 (Box C088)
- Corridor Real Estate Journal, The, 1996 - 1996 (Box C089)
- Corridor Real Estate Journal, The, 1997 - 1997 (Box C090)
- Corridor Real Estate Journal, The, 1998-01 - 1998-06 (Box C091)
- Corridor Real Estate Journal, The, 1998-07 - 1998-12 (Box C092)
- Corridor Real Estate Journal, The, 1999 - 2000 (Box C093)
- Corridor Real Estate Journal, The, 2001 - 2001 (Box C094)
- Cosmos Club Bulletin, 1947 - 1998 (Box C095)
- Cosmos Journal of the Cosmos Club, 1993 - 1999 (Box C096)
- Courier (GWU Medical Center), 1949 - 1964 (Box C097)
- Crecent, The, 1988 - 1990 (Box C098)
- Curtain Up, 1992 - 2000 (Box C099)
- Cultural Alliance News, 1978 - 1981 (Box C100)
- Curbstone Youth News, 1974 - 1976 (Box C101)
- C - Misc 1 (Box C102)
- C - Misc 2 (Box C103)
- C - Misc 3 (Box C104)
- Daily Rag, The, 1972 - 1974 (Box D001)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 1988 - 1990 (Box D002)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 1990 - 1991 (Box D003)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 1992 - 1993 (Box D004)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 1993 - 1995 (Box D005)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 1995 - 1997 (Box D006)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 1997 - 1998 (Box D007)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 1999 - 2000 (Box D008)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2001 - 2002 (Box D009)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2002 - 2005 (Box D010)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2004-01 - 2004-04 (Box D011)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2005 - 2006 (Box D012)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2004-05 - 2004-08 (Box D013)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2007-07 - 2007-09 (Box D014)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2007-10 - 2007-12 (Box D015)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2007 - 2009 (Box D016)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2009 - 2010 (Box D017)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2011 - 2011 (Box D018)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2011-12 - 2012-03 (Box D019)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2012-04 - 2012-07 (Box D020)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2012-08 - 2012-11 (Box D021)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2012-12 - 2013-03 (Box D022)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2013-04 - 2013-07 (Box D023)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2013-08 - 2013-11 (Box D024)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2013-12 - 2014-03 (Box D025)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2014-04 - 2014-07 (Box D026)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2014-08 - 2014-11 (Box D027)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2014-12 - 2015-03 (Box D028)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2015-04 - 2015-07 (Box D029)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2015-08 - 2015-11 (Box D030)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2015-12 - 2016-03 (Box D031)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2016-04 - 2016-07 (Box D032)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2016-08 - 2016-10 (Box D033)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter, 2016-11 - 2017-03-14 (Box D034)
- Daily Washington Law Reporter (Indexes), 1980 - 2007 (Box D035)
- DC Blues Calendar, 2001-02 - 2006-11 (Box D036)
- DC Economy, 1991-09 - 1997 (Box D037)
- DC Gazette, 1972 - 1973 (Box D038)
- DC Gazette, 1986 - 1987 (Box D039)
- DC Health, 1967-07 - 1971-01 (Box D040)
- DC Libraries, 1929-10 - 1952-10 (Box D041)
- DC Libraries, 1953-01 - 1970 (Box D042)
- DC Libraries, 1953-01 - 1955-10 (Box D043)
- DC Libraries, 1956-01 - 1958-10 (Box D044)
- DC Libraries, 1959-01 - 1964-10 (Box D045)
- DC Libraries, 1965-01 - 1967 (Box D046)
- DC Libraries, 1967 - 1968 (Box D047)
- DC Libraries, 1969 - 1970 (Box D048)
- DC Modern Luxury, 2007-07 - 2008-05 (Box D049)
- DC North, 2002-05 - 2008-12 (Box D050)
- DC North, 2009 - 2010-02 (Box D051)
- DC Pipeline, 1973 - 1978-03 (Box D052)
- DC Voter, The, 1933-04-11 - 1950-12 (Box D053)
- DC Voter, The, 1951-01 - 1989-12 (Box D054)
- DC Voter, The, 1990-02 - 2008-02 (Box D055)
- DCPL News, 1946 - 1959 (Box D056)
- Deal Lite (Alice Deal Junior HS), 1958 - 1961 (Box D057)
- District Chronicles, 2001-09-04 - 2014-12-03 (Box D058)
- District Council Journal, 1983 - 1993 (Box D059)
- District Education (DC Public Schools), 1981-10 - 1988-06 (Box D060)
- District Government Employees Mag., 1947-08 - 1961 (Box D061)
- Dist. of Col. Board of Public Welfare, 1946 - 1954 (Box D062)
- District of Columbia Clubwoman, The, 1945-12 - 1948-11 (Box D063)
- District of Columbia Parent-Teacher, 1926 - 1933 (Box D064)
- Dist. of Col. Procurement Digest, 1987-01 - 1987-12 (Box D065)
- Dist. of Col. Procurement Digest, 1988-01 - 1989-12 (Box D066)
- Dist. of Col. Procurement Digest, 1995-09 - 1996-10 (Box D067)
- District of Columbia Prof. Engineer, 1969-01 - 1976-03 (Box D068)
- District of Col. Real Estate Reporter, 1991 - 2000 (Box D069)
- Dist. of Col. Soc. Sons of Amer. Rev., 1923-03 - 1949-12 (Box D070)
- District Teacher, The, 1931 - 1942 (Box D071)
- Dollars and Sense, 1923 - 1951 (Box D072)
- Downtowner, 2003 - 2009 (Box D073)
- Downtowner, 2011 - 2014 (Box D074)
- Dupont Circle Reporter, 1935-10 - 1950-10 (Box D075)
- Dupont Current, 2002-06-05 - 2004-08 (Box D076)
- Dupont Current, 2004-09 - 2005-11 (Box D077)
- Dupont Current, 2007-01 - 2008-12 (Box D078)
- Dupont Current, 2009-01 - 2010-10 (Box D079)
- Dupont Current, 2010-11 - 2012-12 (Box D080)
- Dupont Current, 2013-01 - 2015-01 (Box D081)
- D - Misc 1 (Box D082)
- D - Misc 2 (Box D083)
- D - Misc 3 (Box D084)
- Diplomat, The, 1959-03 - 1966-09 (Box D085)
- Eagle News, 1995 - 1999 (Box E001)
- East of the River, 2001-12 - 2003-12 (Box E002)
- East of the River, 2004-01 - 2005-12 (Box E003)
- East of the River, 2006-01 - 2007-12 (Box E004)
- East of the River, 2008-02 - 2013-12 (Box E005)
- East of the River, 2014-01 - 2016-08 (Box E006)
- Economy Watch, 1991 - 1993 (Box E007)
- Examiner, 2008-12 - 2011-06 (Box E008)
- Examiner, 2011-06 - 2012-02 (Box E009)
- Examiner, 2012-02 - 2012-11 (Box E010)
- Examiner, 2012-12 - 2013-01 (Box E011)
- Express Daily, 2010-10 - 2011-05 (Box E012)
- Express Daily, 2011-06 - 2012-05 (Box E013)
- Express Daily, 2012-06 - 2013-01 (Box E014)
- Express Daily, 2013-02 - 2013-08 (Box E015)
- Express Daily, 2013-09 - 2015-04 (Box E016)
- Express Daily, 2015-05 - 2017-01-27 (Box E017)
- Emblem, 1973-11 - 1973-11 (Box E018)
- Emphasis Employer, 1976-02 - 1977-08 (Box E018)
- Endeavor, The, 1945-08 - 1954-02 (Box E018)
- Examiner, 2013 - 2013 (Box E019)
- Fast Forward, 1995-02 - 1996-10 (Box F001)
- Federal Architect, The, 1937-04 - 1943-07 (Box F002)
- Federation News, 1979-01 - 1991-Summer (Box F003)
- Federation of Citizen Assoc. (Newsltrs), 1941-12 - 1946-01 (Box F004)
- Federation of Citizen Assoc. (Notices), 1935-12 - 1940-12 (Box F005)
- Finder, The, 1947-08 - 1953-12 (Box F007)
- Fire Fighters, 1946-12 - 1974-06 (Box F008)
- First Folio, 1973-05 - 1974-01 (Box F009)
- Foggy Bottom News, 1939-12 - 2003-07 (Box F010)
- Folklore Society of Greater Wash., 1969-06 - 2013-08 (Box F011)
- Folklore Society of Greater Wash., 2013-09 - 2017-03 (Box F012)
- Forecast, 1975-01 - 1977-12 (Box F013)
- Free Voice, 1975-10 - 1982-04 (Box F014)
- Friends of the Public Schools, 1945-01 - 1952-04 (Box F015)
- F - Misc 1 (Box F016)
- Gaceta Iberoamericano, 1989-04 - 2004-01 (Box G001)
- Gallaudet Today, 1970-Summer - 1995-Summer (Box G002)
- Galleries Magazine, 1981-12 - 2016 (Box G003)
- Gay Blade, The, 1969-10 - 1974-06 (Box G004)
- George Washington Unviersity Mag., 1954 - 1971 (Box G005)
- Georgetown Current, The, 2006 - 2008 (Box G006)
- Georgetown Current, The, 2008 - 2009 (Box G007)
- Georgetown Current, The, 2010 - 2011 (Box G008)
- Georgetown Current, The, 2012 - 2013 (Box G009)
- Georgetown Current, The, 2013 - 2015 (Box G010)
- Georgetown Magazine, 1978-09 - 1982-12 (Box G011)
- Georgetown News, 1933 - 1936 (Box G012)
- Georgetown Spectator, 1963-03 - 1971-08 (Box G013)
- Georgetowner, 2004-06 - 2005-12 (Box G014)
- Georgetowner, 2006-12 - 2007-07 (Box G015)
- Georgetowner, 2008-12 - 2013-01 (Box G016)
- Georgetowner, 2014-06 - 2015-02 (Box G017)
- Good Music, 1951-11 - 1955-06 (Box G018)
- Goodwill in Washington, 1935-12 - 1963-Spring (Box G019)
- Grass Roots, 1873-01 - 1974-11 (Box G020)
- Greater Wash. Chamber of Comm., 1920-10 - 1933-12 (Box G021)
- Group Health Association News, 1943-01 - 1973-03 (Box G022)
- Guide to Arts, The, 1978-04 - 1979-03 (Box G023)
- Guide, The, 1939 - 1939 (Box G024)
- Guide, The, 1940 - 1941 (Box G025)
- Guide, The, 1947 - 1948 (Box G026)
- Happy News, 1982-09 - 1987-10 (Box H001)
- Happy News, 1987-11 - 2001-10 (Box H002)
- Harpers Weekly, 1866-06 - 1866-12 (Box H003)
- Harpers Weekly, 1868-01 - 1868-12 (Box H004)
- Helminthological Society of Wash., 1934 - 1971 (Box H005)
- Hill, The, 1977-03 - 1997-10 (Box H006)
- Hillrag, 1977 - 1983 (Box H007)
- Hillrag, 1983 - 1984 (Box H008)
- Hillrag, 1985 - 1989 (Box H009)
- Hillrag, 1991 - 1994 (Box H010)
- Hillrag, 1995 - 1999 (Box H011)
- Hillrag, 2000 - 2004 (Box H012)
- Hillrag, 2005 - 2007 (Box H013)
- Hillrag, 2008 - 2009 (Box H014)
- Hillrag, 2010 - 2011 (Box H015)
- Hillrag, 2012 - 2013 (Box H016)
- Hillrag, 2014 - 2015-07 (Box H017)
- Hilltop, The, 1998-04 - 1999-05 (Box H018)
- Home Builders Monthly, 1944 - 1951 (Box H019)
- Home Builders Monthly, 1952 - 1958 (Box H020)
- Home Builders Monthly, 1959 - 1966 (Box H021)
- Home Builders Monthly, 1969 - 1971 (Box H022)
- Home News, 1925-Winter - 1980-Fall (Box H023)
- Housing Letters, 1935 - 1955 (Box H024)
- Howard University Bulletin, 1898 - 1932 (Box H025)
- Howard University Magazine, 2003 - 2014 (Box H026)
- Hoya, The, 1972 - 1975 (Box H027)
- Hoya, The, 1974-02 - 1979-09 (Box H028)
- H - Misc 1 (Box H029)
- In Our Own Write, 1979 - 1989 (Box I001)
- In the Anacostia, 1988 - 1994 (Box I002)
- Inchoirer, The, 1937-09 - 1941-06 (Box I003)
- Information Bulletin (DC Dept. of VA), 1967 - 1977 (Box I004)
- Insight on Site, 1972-06 - 1973-04 (Box I005)
- Insights (Library of Congress), 1990 - 1997 (Box I006)
- Intercom (DCLA), 1971 - 1974 (Box I007)
- International Student House News, 1947 - 1953 (Box I008)
- InTowner, The, 1970 - 1978 (Box I009)
- InTowner, The, 1979 - 1985 (Box I010)
- InTowner, The, 1986 - 1995 (Box I011)
- InTowner, The, 1996 - 1998 (Box I012)
- InTowner, The, 2000 - 2004 (Box I013)
- InTowner, The, 2004 - 2007 (Box I014)
- Journal of District of Col. Dental Soc., 1936 - 1975 (Box I015)
- Journal of the Bar Assoc. of DC, 1934 - 1939 (Box I016)
- Journal of the Bar Assoc. of DC, 1940 - 1948 (Box I017)
- Journal of the Bar Assoc. of DC, 1949 - 1958 (Box I018)
- Journal of the Bar Assoc. of DC, 1959 - 1970 (Box I019)
- Journal of the Bar Assoc. of DC, 1964 - 1974 (Box I020)
- Journal of the Columbian Ed. of Wash., 1932 - 1949 (Box I021)
- Journal of the Ed. Assoc. of DC, 1932-11 - 1936-06 (Box I022)
- Journal of the Ed. Assoc. of DC, 1936-09 - 1949-06 (Box I023)
- Journal of the Wash. Academy of Sci., 1899 - 1905 (Box I024)
- Journal of the Wash. Academy of Sci., 1906 - 1914 (Box I025)
- Journal of the Wash. Academy of Sci., 1915 - 1924 (Box I026)
- Journal of the Wash. Academy of Sci., 1925 - 1936 (Box I027)
- Journal of the Wash. Academy of Sci., 1937 - 1948 (Box I028)
- Journal of the Wash. Academy of Sci., 1949 - 1959 (Box I029)
- Journal of the Wash. Academy of Sci., 1960 - 1974 (Box I030)
- Journal of the Wash. Academy of Sci., 1976 - 1976 (Box I031)
- K Street Etc., 1990 - 1991 (Box K001)
- Keynotes, 1987 - 1988 (Box K002)
- Kingman Park Civic Association News, 1938 - 1956 (Box K003)
- Labor Market News, 1959 - 1965 (Box L001)
- Latino, El, 1977 - 1979 (Box L002)
- Latino, El, 1983 - 1985 (Box L003)
- Latino, El, 1986-01 - 1986-12 (Box L004)
- Latino, El, 1987-01 - 1987-12 (Box L005)
- Latino, El, 1988-01 - 1988-12 (Box L006)
- Latino, El, 1989-01 - 1989-06 (Box L007)
- Latino, El, 1989-07 - 1989-12 (Box L008)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1927 - 1934 (Box L009)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1935 - 1943 (Box L010)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1944 - 1957 (Box L011)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1958 - 1974 (Box L012)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1962 - 1973 (Box L013)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1974 - 1979 (Box L014)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1980 - 1981 (Box L015)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1982 - 1983 (Box L016)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1984 - 1989 (Box L017)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1990 - 1995 (Box L018)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 1996 - 2000 (Box L019)
- Leaves of Wesley Heights, 2001 - 2006 (Box L020)
- Legal Times, 1987-10 - 1988-03 (Box L021)
- Legal Times, 1988-04 - 1988-10 (Box L022)
- Legal Times, 1989-01 - 1989-07 (Box L023)
- Legal Times, 1989-08 - 1989-12 (Box L024)
- Legal Times, 1990-01 - 1990-04 (Box L025)
- Legal Times, 1990-05 - 1990-08 (Box L026)
- Legal Times, 1990-09 - 1990-12 (Box L027)
- Legal Times, 1991-01 - 1991-05 (Box L028)
- Legal Times, 1991-06 - 1991-08 (Box L029)
- Legal Times, 1991-08 - 1991-12 (Box L030)
- Legal Times, 1992-01 - 1992-06 (Box L031)
- Legal Times, 1992-07 - 1992-12 (Box L032)
- Legal Times, 1993-01 - 1993-03 (Box L033)
- Legal Times, 1993-04 - 1993-06 (Box L034)
- Legal Times, 1993-07 - 1993-12 (Box L035)
- Legal Times, 1994-01 - 1994-06 (Box L036)
- Legal Times, 1994-07 - 1994-12 (Box L037)
- Legal Times, 1995-01 - 1995-03 (Box L038)
- Legal Times, 1995-04 - 1995-06 (Box L039)
- Legal Times, 1995-07 - 1995-09 (Box L040)
- Legal Times, 1995-10 - 1995-12 (Box L041)
- Legal Times, 1996-01 - 1996-04 (Box L042)
- Legal Times, 1996-04 - 1996-06 (Box L043)
- Legal Times, 1996-07 - 1996-09 (Box L044)
- Legal Times, 1996-10 - 1996-12 (Box L045)
- Legal Times, 1997-01 - 1997-03 (Box L046)
- Legal Times, 1997-04 - 1997-06 (Box L047)
- Legal Times, 1997-07 - 1997-09 (Box L048)
- Legal Times, 1997-10 - 1997-12 (Box L049)
- Legal Times, 1998-01 - 1998-03 (Box L050)
- Legal Times, 1998-04 - 1998-06 (Box L051)
- Legal Times, 1998-07 - 1998-12 (Box L052)
- Legal Times, 1999-01 - 1999-12 (Box L053)
- Legal Times, 2000-01 - 2000-12 (Box L054)
- Legal Times, 2001-01 - 2001-12 (Box L055)
- Legal Times, 2002-01 - 2002-12 (Box L056)
- Legal Times, 2003-01 - 2003-12 (Box L057)
- Legal Times, 2004-01 - 2004-12 (Box L058)
- Legal Times, 2005-01 - 2005-12 (Box L059)
- Legal Times, 2006-01 - 2006-12 (Box L060)
- Legal Times, 2007-01 - 2007-12 (Box L061)
- Legal Times, 2008-01 - 2009-04 (Box L062)
- Library of Congress Info. Bulletin, 1990 - 1994 (Box L063)
- Library of Congress Info. Bulletin, 1995 - 1999 (Box L064)
- Local Climatological Data, 1915 - 1947 (Box L065)
- Local Climatological Data, 1968 - 1994 (Box L066)
- Local Climatological Data, 1984 - 1990 (Box L067)
- Mayflower's Log, The, 1925-02 - 1930-03 (Box M001)
- Mayflower's Log, The, 1930-04 - 1935-12 (Box M002)
- Mayflower's Log, The, 1943-12 - 1947-03 (Box M004)
- McLean Gardens News, 1944-04 - 1950-06 (Box M005)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1932 - 1937 (Box M006)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1938 - 1942 (Box M007)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1943 - 1947 (Box M008)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1948 - 1952 (Box M009)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1953 - 1956 (Box M010)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1957 - 1958 (Box M011)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1959 - 1961 (Box M012)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1961 - 1964 (Box M013)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1965 - 1967 (Box M014)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1968 - 1971 (Box M015)
- Medical Annals of the Dist. of Col., 1971 - 1974 (Box M016)
- Men of Washington, 1907 - 1911 (Box M017)